 [
    {
        question: "943 000 000 000 000 stands for. (",
        choiceA: "943 trillion  ",
        choiceB: "943 billion ",
        choiceC: "943 ten million ",
        choiceD: "943 hundred thousand .",
        correct: "A"
    },
    {
        question: "Find the Common Factors  of 24 and 40.(",
        choiceA: "2, 4, 8 ",
        choiceB: "2,3,4,6,12  ",
        choiceC: "4,8,12  ",
        choiceD: "7,12,18",
        correct: "C"
    },
    {
        question: "Find the Least Common Multiple ( LCM ) of  9,10,12 and 15",
        choiceA: "20",
        choiceB: "35",
        choiceC: "105",
        choiceD: "180",
        correct: "D"
    },
    {
        question: "Find the H.C.F  of 63,  42  and  21   ",
        choiceA: "21",
        choiceB: "18",
        choiceC: "24",
        choiceD: "32",
        correct: "C"
    },
    {
        question: "Write 8x8x8x8x8 in index form ",
        choiceA: "8² ",
        choiceB: "8³ ",
        choiceC: "8⁴",
        choiceD: "8⁵",
        correct: "C"
    },
    {
        question: "An integer which could be positive or negative is called a _______ ",
        choiceA: "tens ",
        choiceB: "whole number",
        choiceC: "digit",
        choiceD: "unit",
        correct: "B"


    },
    {
        question: "Number in base two is known as  …………………",
        choiceA: "octeal ",
        choiceB: "duodecimal ",
        choiceC: "binary",
        choiceD: "decimal",
        correct: "D"

    },
    {
        question: "Which of these binary is 24 in base ten ",
        choiceA: "11001₂ ",
        choiceB: "11000₂ ",
        choiceC: "11100₂  ",
        choiceD: "10110₂",
        correct: "A"

    },
    {
        question: "Hexadecimal is a number in base ",
        choiceA: "10",
        choiceB: "12 ",
        choiceC: "2",
        choiceD: "16",
        correct: "B"

    },
    {
        question: "10.	Two-third of the mangoes in a basket are good.If the total number of mangoes in the basket is 42, how many mangoes in the basket are bad? ",
        choiceA: "10 ",
        choiceB: "14",
        choiceC: "15",
        choiceD: "17",
        correct: "B"

    }
];
